<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Groovy | Andreas Arledal]]></title>
  <link href="http://andreasarledal.github.com/blog/categories/groovy/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://andreasarledal.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-01-15T12:12:19+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://andreasarledal.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Andreas Arledal]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gr8 expectations]]></title>
    <link href="http://andreasarledal.github.com/blog/2012/01/15/gr8-expectations/"/>
    <updated>2012-01-15T10:27:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://andreasarledal.github.com/blog/2012/01/15/gr8-expectations</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It's a little late for new years resolutions, but I have some promises to myself for this year strongly connected to this blog and my life as a developer. One of my biggest goals for the year is to take the next step in being a more active contributor to the groovy and grails community. To put the pressure on myself I decided to share those goals here, so here they are:</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Be active on the grails mailing list</h2>

<p>Up until now I haven't been that active on the mailing list, and I really don't know why that is. I'm a frequent reader and it has been of great help many times. From now on I will try to answer at least one question everyother week and ask questions for all problems I can't find a quick answer for.</p>

<h2>Blog and tweet more</h2>

<p>I've started a couple of blogs during the years but I have never really got up to speed with blogging any time. This is something I really would like to change. So, my promise is to write at least one blog post every month about something related to Groovy/Grails.</p>

<h2>Speaking at conferences</h2>

<p>In december last year gave my first presentation ever on a conference at the Groovy and Grails exchange. I think I did ok and learned a lot from the experience. I feel that I have a lot to share and I'm not short of ideas for presentations. My goal is to speak at at least 2 conferences 2012 about at least 2 topics. The gr8conf call for papers is open and I have at least two talk proposals in the making for it.</p>

<h2>Advocating Groovy more active in Sweden</h2>

<p>3 years ago me and <a href="https://twitter.com/#!/xlson" title="@xlson">Leonard Axelsson</a> founded SweGUG and we've had a handful of meetings since with between 8 and 20 attendees. Leonard has done a great job doing most work with organizing thoose meetings. For 2012 I will try to take a more active part in that again. I also hope that we will find someone more who would like to take an active part in this. My personal goal for SweGUG is that we should have at least 5 meeting during the year with one meeting with at least 30 attendees.</p>

<p>With the help of my employer <a href="http://www.find-out.se" title="FindOut Technologies">FindOut Technologies</a> I will try to give a free seminar about grails.</p>

<h2>Contributing</h2>

<p>I've written a few grails plugins for internal use during the years, but besides doing the CSS for the navigation plugin I've never contributed anything that's been made public. This year I will try to write one public plugin.</p>

<p>I will also try to contribute to the grails documentation whenever I find something wrong or missing.</p>

<h2>Personal</h2>

<p>While doing all the above I will also try to spend more time off the computer. 2011 has been a great year when it comes to work and I hope that 2012 will be an equally great year but with one big difference, not that much overtime but instead spending more time with my lovely family without a macbook pro in my lap.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
